# nishant saini

### Relationship Manager at Fitelo

A technological enthusiast Completed master's degree in computer application, i have always wanted to explore new technology and use my skills for providing services. I would be honoured to work with you and expand my skills and experience whilst being an asset to your organization.



nishantsaini009@gmail.com

09027617275

ROORKEE, India

nishant.on.fleek.co/

linkedin.com/in/saininishant09 in

@saininishant09

github.com/nishantsaini09

### **EDUCATION**

# Master of Computer Applications - MCA, Computer Science CHANDIGARH UNIVERSITY

08/2021 - Present 7.64

Courses

Weather App
Cryptocurrency App

# Bachelor of Computer Applications - BCA, Computer Science Quantum University

08/2018 - 08/2021 8.2

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Relationship Manager** Fitelo

06/2022 - Present

Tasks

- Handle client inquiries, concerns, and feedback, demonstrating effective problem-solving skills.
- Regularly track and document client progress, adapting strategies as needed to optimize results.
- Contribute to team meetings and strategy sessions, offering insights to enhance the overall client experience.

# Freelance Expert in Cloud Computing Mere Mentor

12/2022 - Present

Tasks

- Conducted online one-on-one career counseling sessions as a Freelance Expert in Cloud Computing for Mere Mentor
- Provided guidance and insights to clients seeking to make informed career decisions related to cloud computing.
- Developed customized career plans and mind maps to help clients align their career goals with industry trends and opportunities.
- Prepared concise session reports, summarizing key takeaways and recommendations, and submitted them in a timely manner.

# **SKILLS**

CLOUD COMPUTING

WEB DEVELOPMENT

C++

PYTHON

WORDPRESS

## FREELANCING PROJECTS

Property Round

propertyround.com

Varamahalaxmi

varamahalaxmi.in

Nauticalkey

nauticalkey.com

AUTO glaze

autoglazewmt.com

Your Movers

www.yourmovers.com.au

#### CERTIFICATES

30 Days of Google Cloud

Learn to Earn Cloud Challenge by Qwiklabs

Preparing for the Google Cloud Associate Cloud Engineer Exam by Google Cloud

Crash Course on Python

#### LANGUAGES

English

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Hindi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

### **INTERESTS**

Reading books

Movies

Writing

Traveling